Preliminary Guide to the John C. Lilly papers M0786
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 12. Audiovisual media
  - 12.4 Numbered A/V and photographs #1-37
    - 31. Albert Hofmann and John Lilly at Rittematte, Switzerland 1991, Casual Lunch Interview, Conducted by Barbara Lilly and Philip Bailey [1 DVD] (Flat-box 142, Folder 3)
    - 32. Penn and Teller, "Bullshit," Program on Dolphins with John C. Lilly [1 DVD] (Flat-box 142, Folder 4)
    - 33. Creon Levitt Memorial Statement and introduction to Dr. Lilly at "Guilding the Lilly" Celebration, San Francisco, April 2000 [1 DVD] (Flat-box 142, Folder 5)
    - 34. Silence, with John C. Lilly, Japanese Music CD 1993 [Compact disc] (Flat-box 142, Folder 6)
    - 35. Series of notated photographs from birth through final years of Dr John C. Lilly, M.D. (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - 36. Cogitate, The Reel To Reel Tapes of the Experiment [2 12" audio reels] (Flat-box 142, Folder 7)
    - 37. John C. Lilly at the October Gallery 1996 [1 VHS] (Flat-box 142, Folder 8)
- Series 13. Miscellaneous articles, correspondence, etc. [2012-052, 2014-009 addenda]
  - B. Gilbert's Notes (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Hardware/Software Reference/Persons (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - T.t. Brain Disection. Depth elect. position (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Memorial (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - George Toobey (Box 128, Folders 2-3)
  - Geof. Keichley (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Papers (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Letters re: John Lilly (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - School records (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Bazett (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Mayo (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Francis Thornton (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - ECD Nanometer (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Ski Theory (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Silverstein (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Biographical info (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Clippings (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Clippings (Box 129, Folders 1-2)
  - Student letters (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Lilly letter (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Rachel Lilly letters (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Lilly family letters (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Stanford archives, 1995 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Antoinette (Tom) Lilly (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - untitled (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - RCL, Anatomy Drawings, Cartoon (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - JCL Builds Radio Station w/ Friends (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Articles by John C. Lilly (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Reprints J.C. Lilly, 1941-1955 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Dolphins (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Penthouse September 1973 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - John C. Lilly (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - JC Lilly (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Clipping (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Here's the Quadrant (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - This Atalanta's So Sensible (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - International Physiological Conference Belgium (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Au Lutrin qui Montreal 21-1-49 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Medical Fraternities (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Insurance Card (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - Center of the Cyclone (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - The Basic Equipment (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Contact Lists (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Life Magazine (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Norman Viken '41 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - articles, book cover poster, 80th birthday collage 1/6/95 (Flat-box 146)